This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates.
Mokini Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from his crew,
Luffy snuck into the fortress prison impelled down
to rescue his brother Ace, who had been captured by the Navy.
But unbeknownst to Luffy, Ace had already been transferred to Navy Headquarters.
I'm leaving.
Huh?
I'm going to Marineford.
Now attempting to break out of the prison,
Luffy fights his way to level four.
Before he could go any further though,
he was forced to face off with Hannibal, the furious Vice Warden.
This is the Great Fortress of Hell! None shall pass! Now be gone!
And I won't let the world drown in terror by letting prisoners break free!
So like I already said, you won't take a single stab!
The only thing I want is to save my brother, so move it!
Buttercork had it already!
All this blathering about what's right and wrong in the world.
Huh?
If you'd look at the world from outside your damn prison,
you'd see it's not so black and white!
So cut the crack!
Looks like we got you boys right in the middle of something!
Hello, Teach! Mind telling us what the hell you're doing here?
Well, what do you only answer to Blackbeard now?
Blackbeard?
Huh?
So you're...
Blackbeard!
Better make sure you pay your humble respects at his grave, Straw Hat.
He went and took your place for you.
Cause if it weren't for your brother,
you'd be dead and he'd be walking free.
Is that the truth?
Try to kill me now!
Huh?
Come on!
Jet Pistol!
Jet Pistol of Anger!
Luffy versus Blackbeard!
Captain!
I'm not gonna let my brother die!
Come, come!
Jet!
The Black Vortex!
Ah!
Come, come!
Jet!
The Black Vortex!
Straw Boy!
Ah!
Blood!
I thought it was made of rummer!
Ah!
You don't even realize what the hell I just did!
Do you?
That dumb look on your face!
That's the same expression, your brother!
Ah!
What you understand now, you understood the secondary graph.
Not only can my darkness pull you in, it can also absorb your Devil Fruit power!
And that's how I broke your miserable brother.
Now, just like him, your devil-proof powers are about as useless as money to a dickman.
So what? You think that matters?
Luffy, that's enough. Calm yourself.
Let go, David! Get out of my way!
Big boy, open!
Let go of me!
Stop and listen to me! What is your objective here?
Is fighting going to help you accomplish it?
As long as I've known him, Teach has always been a mystery.
Even when he was a nobody on Whitebeard's crew.
I don't know where the Cretan got his powers from, but not even your invincible brother was strong enough to overcome that terrifying darkness.
It's pointless for you to waste your time and energy fighting him. And it sure as hell's not going to do Ace any good. You can't save your brother if you get yourself killed.
You're stronger than I expected, Straw Hack. You got more hockey than you did last time.
Your name is Blackbeard, you said.
Huh?
Then you're the nameless pirate I've heard so much about. The one who was part of Whitebeard's crew until he took my place as warlord.
But this is rather odd. Surely they summoned you to Navy headquarters for the execution. So why are you here? It's clear enough how much you coveted the title of warlord. So why would you risk losing it to come to this dump?
It's all a part of my grand scheme. If you're that interested, I suppose I can lay it out for you. Is that what you want, Mr. Crocodile?
No. No, I'm fine. To be honest, I couldn't care less. Got a heart made of ice. This one does.
Whoa! What the hell? What's happening now?
Warner Magellan is here!
There goes the party.
Hey, Straw Boy! You gotta get out of here! You can't take the risk of Magellan poisoning you again! You were lucky the first time around, but you won't survive another one!
The other one's gonna be here any second! Run!
Come on, guys! Let's gooo!
Who did Magellan's here?
We're saved! We're finally saved!
Magellan. So I finally get to meet the monster.
Head up the stairs!
The bazooka troops have cleared out! There's nothing in our way now!
Ivankov!
You're not getting away from me! I never got that scream out of you, and I don't like being kept waiting.
Please, no, don't! I'm begging you, Princess, please don't do it! Please don't strike me with your whip! I can't bear the pain!
Did something happen while I was gone? Oh, well, I like you better this way! Now stop fighting the inevitable and get over here!
Okay, okay, okay, okay! I give up! I'm coming to you right now, I promise! Not a bad performance! Ha!
Not my whip! Give it back, Ivankov! I mean it!
Actually, why don't we try a little role reversal instead? Since you're such a fan of screaming, let's hear yours!
You may be a princess, but I'll show you why they call me queen! And for your first lesson in etiquette, from now on, call me mistress!
Hee-haw!
How dare you!
Hey, Straw Hats! Hurry up and hit those stairs! Get to level three, okay?
We appreciate you scattering their defense on the staircase. I must at least give you your due on that one.
You helped us out too, you know. This would have been a hell of a lot harder without the panic you caused.
Clear! We've got a straight shot to level three! Freedom, here we come!
Ah!
Crap! It's another freaking demon guard!
It's Minotaurus this time!
What?
Minotaurus?
I'll come out with Kenpo!
Memoirs of the Winter Skies!
You ready, Straw Hats?
Ken-do!
All right!
Now go!
Ah!
Are you serious? Those monsters ain't a devil fruit!
We need to hurry this up.
Who knows how little time we've got before the other three recover.
Also, if you're gonna piss your pants, don't waste it on them.
Because we've already got the boss of hell hot on our tail.
Warden Magellan, sir.
I just received a report that Blackbeard has already infiltrated this floor.
And he's at the staircase to level three as we speak.
I put that lunatic sheet of you in charge of holding them back.
Was he defeated?
This is the monitoring room!
What now?
We've got a problem, sir.
We've lost the visual feed in all of our monitors.
Someone broke the vision receiver transponder's tail.
And, if that wasn't already bad enough,
all communication channels to Navy HQ have been cut off.
So we can't even contact...
What's going on here?
Hey! Keep talking!
What's happening?
Do you know who's behind the blackout?
A lick.
Can't have you blowing my cover.
I want this to be a surprise for the boss man.
We've lost communication with communications!
Get someone up there to find out what's going on.
Yes, sir!
It just keeps getting worse.
The only way Blackbeard could have made it to this floor
is if he overcame the toxic blockades I placed over the exits on level two.
And that would make level two defenseless.
None of our plans are working.
We were careless enough to let a single rat sneak in.
And now we're up to our necks and vermin.
Buggy!
Mr. Three!
The queen for genius!
We made it, guys!
We fought by killing!
Here we are!
Level one!
Yay!
All right!
We're going to get to feel the sun on our skin, and who do we have to thank?
Our brave and brilliant savior, Captain Buggy!
I still can't believe that poison block vanished on its own.
We are some lucky SOBs, you know that?
And they think you did it.
Lucky SOBs indeed!
Whoa!
I'm saving Ace!
I'll find a way!
I ain't gonna stop you, kid.
You give it your best.
Nothing's impossible in this world, after all.
But I've already told you that.
Remember Sky Island?
Sky Island?
What an idiot!
You can't be there, kid.
I can't believe you guys are putting open to such a ridiculous legend like an island in the sky!
Thing is, the time of pirates' dreams are over!
So when I see people chasing dreams of One Piece, I get disgusted!
Loopy!
The Sky Island does exist!
Got something you wanna say?
This new era they keep rambling on and on about is a load of crap!
The era when pirates' dream of treasure will come to an end!
Yeah, right!
Ha ha ha!
Yeah!
Right!
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha!
The Sky Island does exist.
Got something you want to say?
This new era they keep rambling on and on about is a load of crap.
The era when pirates dream of treasure will come to an end?
Yeah, right!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
The dreams of pirates will never end!
Am I right?
And just like Sky Island, the One Piece is really out there.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
I can't wait for you to see what we've got in store!
Trust me, you're going to be impressed.
In a few hours, we're going to put on a show so explosive
that it'll shake the whole damn world.
Ignore him, Luffy. Come on.
Yee-haw!
Keep moving, boys.
Straight to level three.
Crap! We're dead!
We can't defeat him!
We're trapped on this floor!
The further he comes down,
the more he keeps pushing us back!
No! We're helpless against him!
What do we do?
Wait, Straw Hat, you don't want to fight that beast!
Hold on, Straw Boy! I can help!
Back off!
Huh?
Just wait.
The last thing you want to do is step in this path now.
What's that supposed to mean?
We're partners!
He needs me!
You're in my way.
Huh?
Straw Boy, no!
Ah!
erradoísimo
Second gear!
Gum gum!
Jack!
Pitones!
Err!
I'm coming, Ace!
Did that just happen?
He finished off that monster with a single punch.
I heard this guy was tough, but that's just plain crazy.
Nice, Straw Boy.
Okay, that's that.
What's everyone just standing around for?
Fuck! Let's skedaddle!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Warden!
Oh! Oh! Can you please get me down from here? Stop staring, you creeps! Help me!
Calm down. Tell me what happened to you, Sadie.
That Tammy Von Cuff beat me and tied me up! Just get me down!
Do you know how humiliating it is to do this to a dominatrix?
Help her, man. I don't have time to deal with this.
Yes, sir! Right away!
I've got a funny feeling you're Magellan.
And I'm guessing you're Blackbeard.
Hit the nail right on the head, pal.
Hydra!
I'm too busy trying to run this prison to even bother asking what you're doing here.
Oh! Oh! What is this stuff?
Oh! Dammit! It's gonna be some kind of poison!
Get back here!
Hannibal.
I'm impressed with how long you held out.
I'll take the rest from here.
Is the Vice Warden all right, sir?
Oh, no. He looks terrible.
Quit gawking and help him out.
Yes, sir!
Vice Warden! Just hang in there, okay? Can you hear me, sir?
You can't die, Hannibal.
You're the only one who can possibly take my place.
Straw Hat.
How the hell could you possibly survive after I poisoned you?
There's no doubt that he's the one who caused all this mayhem.
The next chance I get, nothing will stop me from taking his life.
Straw Hat!
You hear that? Magellan's coming!
That came from the foot of the stairs!
We're all dead if it catches up to us!
The poison guy!
I promise you this, Straw Hat!
You will never escape this prison!
Luffy and company finally make their way through level three.
Ivankov has Inazuma sealed the stairs to slow Magellan down
and remains behind to face him in battle
while the others make their escape to the top of the prison.
However, even his new Kama Kenpo may prove no match for the Warden's deadly poison.
On the next Wood Piece, Stop Magellan!
Eva's esoteric technique explodes!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!